[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New York"]}, "docId": "130305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 49, "question": "If you're sitting here in New York, as we are, is it going to be a huge tub load coming our way?", "question_tokens": ["If", "you", "'re", "sitting", "here", "in", "New", "York", ",", "as", "we", "are", ",", "is", "it", "going", "to", "be", "a", "huge", "tub", "load", "coming", "our", "way", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 50, "answer": "No, not for New York.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "not", "for", "New", "York", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New York"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 100, "question": "Was that your experience?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "that", "your", "experience", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 101, "answer": "Yes, he could be.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "he", "could", "be", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Che Guevara"], "LOCATION": ["Latin America"], "PERSON": ["Fidel Castro"]}, "docId": "130305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 145, "question": "But how do you think history will judge him?", "question_tokens": ["But", "how", "do", "you", "think", "history", "will", "judge", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 146, "answer": "Well, he's a classic Caudillo of Latin America, a strongman, who was infatuated with Che Guevara and Fidel Castro.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "he", "'s", "a", "classic", "Caudillo", "of", "Latin", "America", ",", "a", "strongman", ",", "who", "was", "infatuated", "with", "Che", "Guevara", "and", "Fidel", "Castro", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 223, "question": "Yes, Ali, there is a disconnect, isn't there?", "question_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "Ali", ",", "there", "is", "a", "disconnect", ",", "is", "n't", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 224, "answer": "Yes, sure.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "sure", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ali"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 233, "question": "And the poor getting poorer?", "question_tokens": ["And", "the", "poor", "getting", "poorer", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 234, "answer": "I'll say a few things.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'ll", "say", "a", "few", "things", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["S&P"]}, "docId": "130305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "CD", ",", "CC", "JJS", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 236, "question": "So is that combined an indicator of the strengthening economy?", "question_tokens": ["So", "is", "that", "combined", "an", "indicator", "of", "the", "strengthening", "economy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "VBZ", "IN", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 237, "answer": "Well, the thing is, when you look at the Dow, you look at the S&P 500, or most major companies, much of their revenue comes from the rest of the world.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "thing", "is", ",", "when", "you", "look", "at", "the", "Dow", ",", "you", "look", "at", "the", "S", "&", "P", "500", ",", "or", "most", "major", "companies", ",", "much", "of", "their", "revenue", "comes", "from", "the", "rest", "of", "the", "world", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 247, "question": "Kai, if you -- if you have got a bit of cash -- and many Americans don't, but if you do have a bit of cash at the moment, is it a good or a terrible time to invest in the stock market?", "question_tokens": ["Kai", ",", "if", "you", "--", "if", "you", "have", "got", "a", "bit", "of", "cash", "--", "and", "many", "Americans", "do", "n't", ",", "but", "if", "you", "do", "have", "a", "bit", "of", "cash", "at", "the", "moment", ",", "is", "it", "a", "good", "or", "a", "terrible", "time", "to", "invest", "in", "the", "stock", "market", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ":", "CC", "JJ", "NNPS", "VBP", "RB", ",", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 248, "answer": "Oh, for crying out loud do not put your money in the stock market right now.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "for", "crying", "out", "loud", "do", "not", "put", "your", "money", "in", "the", "stock", "market", "right", "now", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "130305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "TO", "RB", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "WP", "VBZ", "NNS", "VBP", "CC", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 315, "question": "How are you going to change the way Americans think about guns?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "you", "going", "to", "change", "the", "way", "Americans", "think", "about", "guns", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NNPS", "VBP", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 316, "answer": "Well, I think if you go back to just being consistent with culture, culture is really what makes things change and stick in America.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "if", "you", "go", "back", "to", "just", "being", "consistent", "with", "culture", ",", "culture", "is", "really", "what", "makes", "things", "change", "and", "stick", "in", "America", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 350, "question": "That's the realistic goal, right, is what you're trying to do?", "question_tokens": ["That", "'s", "the", "realistic", "goal", ",", "right", ",", "is", "what", "you", "'re", "trying", "to", "do", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "RB", ",", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 351, "answer": "Our fight isn't against guns.", "answer_tokens": ["Our", "fight", "is", "n't", "against", "guns", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", ":"], "qSentId": 379, "question": "Is it time to have just as compelling and controversial advertising relating to gun violence?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "time", "to", "have", "just", "as", "compelling", "and", "controversial", "advertising", "relating", "to", "gun", "violence", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "TO", "VB", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 380, "answer": "The problem with -- it depends on the kind of --", "answer_tokens": ["The", "problem", "with", "--", "it", "depends", "on", "the", "kind", "of", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "IN", "WP", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 459, "question": "What I'm interested in now is why you have quit the NRA?", "question_tokens": ["What", "I", "'m", "interested", "in", "now", "is", "why", "you", "have", "quit", "the", "NRA", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "RB", "VBZ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 460, "answer": "Because all you ever hear about is fund-raising, for what purpose, I'm not really sure.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "all", "you", "ever", "hear", "about", "is", "fund-raising", ",", "for", "what", "purpose", ",", "I", "'m", "not", "really", "sure", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["NRA"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VB", "DT", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", ",", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "CD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 465, "question": "Do you think it would change their PR, if nothing else if they really started to take seriously advertising and promoting safe gun use?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "it", "would", "change", "their", "PR", ",", "if", "nothing", "else", "if", "they", "really", "started", "to", "take", "seriously", "advertising", "and", "promoting", "safe", "gun", "use", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP$", "NNP", ",", "IN", "NN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "RB", "VBG", "CC", "VBG", "NN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 466, "answer": "Well, they do, do that in their marksmanship program, which you've got to enroll in one of their marksmanship courses to get that.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "they", "do", ",", "do", "that", "in", "their", "marksmanship", "program", ",", "which", "you", "'ve", "got", "to", "enroll", "in", "one", "of", "their", "marksmanship", "courses", "to", "get", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 470, "question": "Do you think many feel unsettled after Sandy Hook the leadership went so aggressively on the front foot and the result was simply the selling of a lot more weapons?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "many", "feel", "unsettled", "after", "Sandy", "Hook", "the", "leadership", "went", "so", "aggressively", "on", "the", "front", "foot", "and", "the", "result", "was", "simply", "the", "selling", "of", "a", "lot", "more", "weapons", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RBR", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 471, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "NN", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 486, "question": "Where are you going to get the money to buy them?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "are", "you", "going", "to", "get", "the", "money", "to", "buy", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 487, "answer": "Well, I guess the assault weapons ban would apply to future sales.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "guess", "the", "assault", "weapons", "ban", "would", "apply", "to", "future", "sales", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "VBG", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 492, "question": "If I could ask you to say one thing that you felt would be most constructive to making America a less violent country in terms the of gun violence, what would you say?", "question_tokens": ["If", "I", "could", "ask", "you", "to", "say", "one", "thing", "that", "you", "felt", "would", "be", "most", "constructive", "to", "making", "America", "a", "less", "violent", "country", "in", "terms", "the", "of", "gun", "violence", ",", "what", "would", "you", "say", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "CD", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "MD", "VB", "RBS", "JJ", "TO", "VBG", "NNP", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "DT", "IN", "NN", "NN", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 493, "answer": "One would be to enforce the existing laws.", "answer_tokens": ["One", "would", "be", "to", "enforce", "the", "existing", "laws", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "TO", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "IN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 539, "question": "Is preparation in the end the single-most important thing?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "preparation", "in", "the", "end", "the", "single-most", "important", "thing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 540, "answer": "I think preparation is the key to success and you lay it all out, as you well know, as we describe in the book.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "preparation", "is", "the", "key", "to", "success", "and", "you", "lay", "it", "all", "out", ",", "as", "you", "well", "know", ",", "as", "we", "describe", "in", "the", "book", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "DT", "VBP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 546, "question": "What would you get them to do, these politicians, to try to work better for the cause of America?", "question_tokens": ["What", "would", "you", "get", "them", "to", "do", ",", "these", "politicians", ",", "to", "try", "to", "work", "better", "for", "the", "cause", "of", "America", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", ",", "DT", "NNS", ",", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 547, "answer": "Well, we all want that.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "we", "all", "want", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New York"]}, "docId": "130305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBZ", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBD", "PRP$", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "VBN", ",", "JJ", "IN", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 554, "question": "How does that work?", "question_tokens": ["How", "does", "that", "work", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 555, "answer": "Well, the way that works is when I first went to New York, what I wanted was our players to be focused, enthusiastic about coming to work.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "way", "that", "works", "is", "when", "I", "first", "went", "to", "New", "York", ",", "what", "I", "wanted", "was", "our", "players", "to", "be", "focused", ",", "enthusiastic", "about", "coming", "to", "work", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["NFL"]}, "docId": "130305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "DT", "NNP", "VBZ", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 583, "question": "How do you get them to understand what discipline is like off the field in their real lives?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "get", "them", "to", "understand", "what", "discipline", "is", "like", "off", "the", "field", "in", "their", "real", "lives", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "WP", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 584, "answer": "Well, that's not an easy thing, but you know, when you're talking about this gun culture, the NFL has strong rules against that.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "that", "'s", "not", "an", "easy", "thing", ",", "but", "you", "know", ",", "when", "you", "'re", "talking", "about", "this", "gun", "culture", ",", "the", "NFL", "has", "strong", "rules", "against", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 607, "question": "Stage, movies, the Oscars, TV, you're doing all of that, are you, Kristin?", "question_tokens": ["Stage", ",", "movies", ",", "the", "Oscars", ",", "TV", ",", "you", "'re", "doing", "all", "of", "that", ",", "are", "you", ",", "Kristin", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", ",", "NNS", ",", "DT", "NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "IN", "DT", ",", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 608, "answer": "I try.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "try", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Kristin"], "LOCATION": ["Oscars"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 609, "question": "How are you?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 610, "answer": "I'm so good, but I was just hoping that this time --", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "so", "good", ",", "but", "I", "was", "just", "hoping", "that", "this", "time", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 617, "question": "How are you?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 618, "answer": "I'm good.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "good", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 628, "question": "Do you have any problems with what he did?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "have", "any", "problems", "with", "what", "he", "did", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 629, "answer": "HENOWETH: Well, first of all, I'm a woman so I have boobs and I don't really know the big deal.", "answer_tokens": ["HENOWETH", ":", "Well", ",", "first", "of", "all", ",", "I", "'m", "a", "woman", "so", "I", "have", "boobs", "and", "I", "do", "n't", "really", "know", "the", "big", "deal", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 639, "question": "What does it say about America today?", "question_tokens": ["What", "does", "it", "say", "about", "America", "today", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 640, "answer": "You know, I'd be a liar if I didn't say that it was interesting.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "'d", "be", "a", "liar", "if", "I", "did", "n't", "say", "that", "it", "was", "interesting", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mark Burnett"]}, "docId": "130305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 649, "question": "Doesn't it look good?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "n't", "it", "look", "good", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 650, "answer": "Well, it's a classic Mark Burnett production, completely over the top, fabulous costumes, beautiful people.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "'s", "a", "classic", "Mark", "Burnett", "production", ",", "completely", "over", "the", "top", ",", "fabulous", "costumes", ",", "beautiful", "people", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 656, "question": "It's good news, right?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "good", "news", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 657, "answer": "It's good news.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "good", "news", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 660, "question": "On a scale of 1 to 10, how is my accent?", "question_tokens": ["On", "a", "scale", "of", "1", "to", "10", ",", "how", "is", "my", "accent", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "CD", "TO", "CD", ",", "WRB", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 661, "answer": "Eight, pretty awful.", "answer_tokens": ["Eight", ",", "pretty", "awful", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 662, "question": "I'm going to play at London, Manchester, Edinburgh so tell me from London to Manchester, how many hours is that?", "question_tokens": ["I", "'m", "going", "to", "play", "at", "London", ",", "Manchester", ",", "Edinburgh", "so", "tell", "me", "from", "London", "to", "Manchester", ",", "how", "many", "hours", "is", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "RB", "RB", "PRP", "IN", "NNP", "TO", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 663, "answer": "They don't use language like that on stage.", "answer_tokens": ["They", "do", "n't", "use", "language", "like", "that", "on", "stage", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["London", "Manchester", "Edinburgh", "London", "Manchester"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 671, "question": "Isn't it great?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "n't", "it", "great", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 672, "answer": "I love all of the casts and you have this terrible accident.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "love", "all", "of", "the", "casts", "and", "you", "have", "this", "terrible", "accident", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "RB", "CD", "TO", "CD", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "WP", "VBN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 683, "question": "What did you feel?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "you", "feel", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 684, "answer": "I was out for about six to seven minutes and I woke up and they said what happened and they said you fell.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "out", "for", "about", "six", "to", "seven", "minutes", "and", "I", "woke", "up", "and", "they", "said", "what", "happened", "and", "they", "said", "you", "fell", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "NN", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "RBR", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 696, "question": "You've still got repercussions?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'ve", "still", "got", "repercussions", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 697, "answer": "HENOWETH: My brain issues are much better, but it does take some time.", "answer_tokens": ["HENOWETH", ":", "My", "brain", "issues", "are", "much", "better", ",", "but", "it", "does", "take", "some", "time", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 705, "question": "Are they going to show the scenes of what happened?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "they", "going", "to", "show", "the", "scenes", "of", "what", "happened", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "WP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 706, "answer": "Yes, they showed it.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "they", "showed", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]